据说西部是建立在传说上
It's said that the West was built on legends.
而传说协助我们解读超自然的事物
Tall tales that help us make sense of things too great...
或骇人听闻的事
...or too terrifying to believe.
这是关于灵魂骑士的传说
This is the legend of the Ghost Rider.
传说中，每一代都会有一个灵魂骑士
Story goes that every generation has one.
受诅咒的灵魂，在人世间奔驰
Some damned soul, cursed to ride the earth...
兑现魔鬼的契约
...collecting on the devil's deals.
很多年前 有一个灵魂骑士被派去圣凡冈萨村
Many years ago, a Ghost Rider was sent to the village of San Venganza...
兑现一份上千条灵魂的恶魔契约
...to fetch a contract won'th 1000 evil souls.
但那份契约的力量太庞大
But that contract was so powerful...
他知道绝不能让恶魔得到它
...he knew he could never let the devil get his hands on it.
于是，他做了一件灵魂骑士们从未做过的事
So he did what no Rider has ever done before:
他从恶魔手中逃脱了
He outran the devil himself.
传说最奇妙的地方在于…
The thing about legends is...
有时候，它们是真的
...sometimes they're true.
《恶灵骑士》
女士们，先生们
Ladies and gentlemen...
最惊险神奇的
...the amazing, blazing...
摩托车特技！
...stunt cycle spectacular!
请为巴顿和爆火强尼鼓掌吧
How about a big round of applause for Barton and Johnny Blaze?
让我听听你们的掌声
Let's hear it for them, folks!
你很拽呀，小子！
You're a hotshot, ain't you, boy?
乳臭未干的家伙，自以为无所不知
Young, think you know everything there is to know.
自以为可以长生不老，是不是？
Think you're gonna live forever. Is that about right?
- 拜托，老爸，我只是玩玩而已 - 问题不在这里
- Come on, Dad. It was a patch of dirt. - That's not the point.
问题是，我们才表演了不到一周
Point is, we've been doing this act less than a week.
你却已经在鬼混了
You're already screwing around.
- 我那么做只是为了观众 - 我很清楚你是为了谁
- I was just doing it for the crowd. - We both know why you done it.
你以为你坐在轮椅上时她还会陪着你吗？
You think she's gonna stand by you when you're in a wheelchair?
你再拽呀！
Huh, hotshot?
儿子，在生活中你做的每件事 每个选择都其结果
Son, everything you do in life, every choice you make has a consequence.
做事不用大脑
When you do things without thinking...
只会被命运牵着走，而非自己去主导命运
...you ain't making the choice, the choice is making you.
- 明白吗？ - 当然
- You understand that? - Yeah, sure.
什么？
What?
我说: “是的，先生”
I said, "Yes, sir."
嘿，老爸 让我偶尔骑“葛瑞丝”去兜兜风，你觉得如何？
Hey, Dad, you think maybe I could take Grace for a ride sometime?
你觉得你是个 可以驾驭“葛瑞丝”的男子汉了？
Think you're man enough for Grace?
当然是
Hell, yeah.
我可不这么想
Well, I don't.
嗨，强尼
Hey, Johnny.
嗨，罗珊
Hey, Roxie.
去吧
Go on.
(强尼和罗珊 天荒地老)
嘿！
Hey.
怎么了，罗珊
What's wrong, Roxie?
我要走了
I'm leaving.
什么？
What?
我爸要把我送去跟我妈住
My dad's sending me to live with my mom.
- 什么时候？ - 很快
- When? - Soon.
那我们呢？
What about us?
他说你配不上我
He says you're not good enough for me.
你只是一段插曲罢了
That you're just a phase.
我们该怎么办，强尼？
So what are we gonna do, Johnny?
我们一起走，骑上摩托车远走高飞
We'll leave. We'll jump on the bike and just keep going.
那你爸呢？表演呢？
But what about your dad? What about the show?
他不需要我，他不需要任何人
He doesn't need me. He doesn't need anybody.
明天中午，我们在这里会合
Tomorrow, noon. We'll meet here.
（父子飞越烈火）
（癌细胞已经扩散）
几点了？
What time is it?
很晚了
It's late.
你要去哪？
Where you going?
哪都不去，老爸
Nowhere, Dad.
我哪都不去
I'm going nowhere.
差太远了
Far out.
- 爆火强尼 - 是的！
- Johnny Blaze. - Yeah.
我今天看了你的表演
Caught your show today.
我来是想告诉你，我很欣赏你的骑术
Just wanted to tell you how much I enjoyed watching you ride.
哦，谢谢！
Oh, thanks.
也许有一天你会为我骑车
Perhaps you'd ride for me one day.
你也是排节目的？
You run a show?
世上最好的节目
Greatest show on earth.
谢谢，不必了
Thanks, but no thanks.
怎么了，强尼？
What's wrong, Johnny?
在担心你爸爸？
Worried about your father?
你怎么知道？
What do you know about that?
连瞎子也看得出来他病了
Even a blind man could see he's sick.
癌症的特点就是长期的
Thing about cancer is the time it takes...
对亲人的折磨
...the toll on the loved ones.
生活为之改变
Lives that are altered.
计划不得不变更
Plans that have to be changed.
强尼！
Johnny...
如果我能帮你爸爸…
...what if I could help your dad?
是吗？怎么帮？
Yeah? How?
怎么帮不重要
How is not important.
重要的是，如果我能治好他
What if I could make him better?
让他恢复健康
Give him back his health?
你愿意跟我谈个交易吗？
Would you be willing to make a deal?
开个价吧
Name your price.
我就要…
I'll take...
你的灵魂
...your soul.
好！
Okay.
明天一早，你父亲就会健康的像匹马
By sunrise tomorrow, your father will be healthy as a horse.
而摆在你面前的将会是一个完整的人生
And you will have your whole life ahead of you.
这需要你来抉择，强尼
It's your choice, Johnny.
而你只要，签个名
All you have to do is sign.
哦，这样就可以了
Oh, that'll do just fine.
可恶！
Damn.
早安，睡美人
Morning, sleeping beauty.
爸？
Dad?
- 你看起来… - 气色很好，对吧？
- You look... - Great, right?
今早医生帮我检查时也是这么说的
Least that's what the doc said when he looked at my x-rays this morning.
- 你在说什么？ - 我最近病了，孩子
- What are you talking about? - I've been sick, son.
但在我鼓起勇气告诉你之前
When I finally get up the nerve to tell you about it...
就已经康复了
...l'm not anymore.
我也无法解释，不过我觉得自己健康的像匹马
I can't explain it. But I feel healthy as a horse.
走吧，臭小子，我还得表演呢
Now, come on, hotshot. I got a show to do.
一周以来就属这场观众最多 你知道我在想什么吗？
Biggest crowd of the week. Hey, you know what I was thinking about?
一个新特技，把我们推向巅峰
A new stunt. Put us over the top!
伟大的一跃，你我各在一边
Be a jump: Me on one side, you on the other.
用直升机来代替汽车或者火圈
Instead of the cars or the ring of fire, a helicopter.
对，那样肯定酷毙了，你认为呢？
Yeah. That'd be pretty cool, don't you think?
嗨，你只剩2分钟了 快穿上你的行头，儿子，否则…
Hey, you got two minutes to get in your suit, son, or you're...
罗珊的父亲要把她送走
Roxanne's dad is sending her away.
如果我们现在不走，就来不及了
If we don't leave now, it will be too late.
很好，真是伟大啊 两个一无所有的小毛孩搞私奔
Well, that's great, boy. That's great. Two kids on the run with nothing.
如果你的目的是两人最后在一起 最好别搞这一套
If your goal is to end up together, that'll make sure it doesn't happen!
我宁愿铤而走险，也比在愚蠢的狂欢节上
I'd rather take my chances with her than to waste my whole life...
表演飞车特技，浪费我的人生强
...jumping bikes at some stupid carnival.
爸，这样的日子我受够了
Dad, I want something better than that.
她老爸会在你们到达郡界之前 就叫警察把你们逮捕了
Her old man will have the cops on you before you get to county line.
那么我最好马上出发
I guess I'd better get going then.
嘿，臭小子
Hey, hotshot.
你骑葛瑞丝吧！
You take Grace.
至少它会让你有个好的开端
At least you'll have a good head start.
女士们，先生们，爆火巴顿
Ladies and gentlemen, Barton Blaze!
女士们，先生们，请向出口处移动
Ladies and gentlemen, head for the exits.
请保持冷静
Please stay calm.
爸？爸，没事的，我在这儿 我在这儿，没事的
Dad? Dad, it's all right, I'm here. I'm here, it's gonna be okay.
爸？
Dad?
爸？爸？
Dad? Dad?
你死了对我就没用了
You're no good to me dead.
你...你杀了他
You... You killed him.
我已经治好了他的癌症
I cured his cancer.
我的承诺仅此而已
That was the deal.
但我不能让他妨碍到我们
But I couldn't let him come between us.
你这个混蛋
You son of a bitch.
总有一天，当我需要你的时候
One day, when I need you...
我会再来的
...I will come.
但在那之前，我会…
Until then, I'll be...
我会看着你
I'll be watching.
忘记你的朋友
Forget about friends.
忘记你的家庭
Forget about family.
忘记你的爱情
Forget about love.
你是我的，爆火强尼
You're mine, Johnny Blaze.
你不能活在恐惧中
You can't live in fear.
不能活在恐惧中
强尼！强尼！
Johnny, Johnny! Johnny, Johnny!
Johnny, Johnny!
爆火强尼！
Johnny Blaze!
好样的！强尼！好！
Yeah, Johnny! Yeah!
女士们，先生们
Ladies and gentlemen...
请留在原地，让急救人员通过
...please stay off the field to allow paramedics through.
噢，天啊！噢，天啊！JB！
Oh, God. Oh, God. JB!
JB，跟我说说话！
JB, talk to me, man!
见鬼，车子没事吧？
Heck, is the bike okay?
是的！是的！
Yeah. Yeah.
车子没事，噢，天啊！
Bike's fine. Oh, God.
谢谢！
Thank you.
回家吧！
Let's go home.
让我听听你们的掌声
Let's hear it for him, folks.
不可思议的，爆火强尼
The amazing Johnny Blaze!
强尼，你把我们吓了一大跳 当时发生了什么？
Johnny, you gave us all a big scare. What happened out there tonight?
嘿，JB不接受采访的，好吗？ 对不起，借过
Hey, JB don't do interviews, all right? I'm sorry. Excuse me.
（欢迎来到德州）
（爆火车队）
来啊，上啊
Yeah, come on, come on.
前轮着地啊！噢！可恶！
Get the front end down. Damn it.
爆火出局了
Blaze is down.
- 你这么喜欢撞车啊？ - 那你呢？
- Have you tried not crashing? - Have you?
你就不能跟他们一样喝瓶啤酒休息一下吗？
Why don't you have a beer and relax like everybody else, huh?
你知道酒精只会让我做恶梦
You know alcohol gives me nightmares.
人各有所好！
To each his own.
等一下，转回去
Oh, wait, could you go back?
探索频道今晚有个关于吼猴的特辑
There's a howler monkey special on Discovery Channel tonight.
- 伙计们，看！ - 极限运动场中会出现各种事故
- Guys, hey. - We've seen big moves and crashes.
当问到那些车手，他们最崇拜的人时
But ask these riders who it is they look up to...
一致的答案却是从未出场比赛过的人 “爆火强尼”
...and the answer's a man who's not even competing here, Johnny Blaze.
是啊，因为他正坐在这儿
Yeah, that's because he's right here!
史上最棒的特技车手
Greatest stunt rider of all time...
…但我们不知道的是 爆火强尼还能死里逃生多少次
...but what we don't know is how much longer can Blaze cheat death.
- 评论家称之为付费观赏的飞车自杀秀 - 看那个猴子节目吧
- Critics call it pay-per-view suicide... - Put the monkey show on.
麦克，看猴子节目？
Mack, the monkey show?
…似乎根本不关心自己的死活
With no regard for his own life.
他们都叫他无敌先生 而在他的下一次跳越中
They call him Mr. Invincible, and he'll have to be at his next jump...
爆火强尼将试图飞跃
...when Johnny Blaze will attempt to clear...
从球门到球门，一整个足球场的距离
...the length of a football field from field goal to field goal.
怎么了？
What?
怎么了？在像今天的那种情况下 你早就该死了
"What." You should be taking a dirt nap after that ragdoll today.
我只是幸运而已
I got lucky.
是的，我有只猎犬的名字也叫“幸运” 他只有一只眼睛，而且连蛋蛋都没了
No, I got a hunting dog named Lucky. He's got one eye and no nuts.
光靠运气是不够的，强尼 一定是有个天使在守护你
Luck don't cover it, JB. Man, you got an angel looking after you.
- 也许吧 - 麦克，你玩不玩？
- Yeah, maybe. - Mack, you in?
我要玩
Yeah. Yeah, I'm in.
让开点，女士们，怎么玩？
Scoot over, ladies. What's the ante?
玩梭哈
Five card draw.
或许是别的什么
Maybe it's something else.
给你
There you go.
你可真够慢的
Took you long enough.
小子，我想你迷路了吧
I think you might be lost, boy.
你聋了还是怎么了？
You deaf or something?
这里只准天使进入
Angels only in there.
天使？真的？
Angels. Really?
没错，你不爽吗？
Yeah, really. You got a problem with that?
说实话
As a matter of fact...
我是不爽
...I do.
我爱死你住的地方了，强尼
Yep. Love your neighborhood, Johnny.
一派和谐友善的景象
Real friendly around here.
看来你还是没给你家的电梯上锁 很好，很好！
Oh, I see you still haven't gotten a lock for your lift. That's great, great.
但你有很多贵重的摩托车在这里 我跟你说过多少次了？
You've got a lot of expensive bikes in here, I told you. How many times?
JB，我以前就说过，现在再说一次
Well, JB, I said it before, I'll say it again:
你这里需要有个女人在，阴阳调和一下
This place could use a womars touch.
- 你也一样 - 那倒是
- So could you. - Heard that.
很好，五分之四 再摔一辆就收集全套了
All right, four out of five. Wreck one more and you get the whole set.
看来你总算找到书的用途了
Well, I'm glad to see you found use for your books.
要吃软糖吗？
You want some jellies?
不，我才不要你的烂糖果
No. I don't want none of your stupid candy.
其实，我想跟你谈一件很重要的事
I wanna talk to you about something kind of serious.
麦克，我正在想办法放松
I'm trying to relax, Mack.
是，我明白… 一会儿就好
Yeah, I understand. All right? It's just gonna take a second.
关于你爸逝世周年的飞车表演
It's about you jumping on the anniversary of your dad's accident.
我，我可以把音乐停一下吗？
Can I just turn this music off for a minute?
我要你踢的高一些，能吗？
I want you to kick higher for me. Can you get higher?
这个飞越，伙计，我们…
This jump, man, we...
上啊，打它！
Come on! Hit it!
麦克 如果你再敢碰那卡朋特的歌或那猩猩节目
Mack, you touch the Carpenters or that chimp video again...
- 就等着吃我的拳头吧 - 这次的飞越太疯狂了
- and we got a scrap on our hands. - This jump is nuts. All right, man?
我是说，飞越整个球场 现在你又要在中间加车子
I mean, field goal to field goal, and now you're adding cars?
我说，你到底想要证明什么
I mean, what are you trying to prove?
证明确实是我
That it's me.
是你？
That it's you?
在骑车
Riding the bike.
当然是你，还会有谁
Of course it's you, man. Who the hell else is it gonna be?
你知道吗？你现在真的把我搞毛了
You know what, you're freaking me out.
因为你没事在看这些
You're freaking me out because you're reading...
邪里邪气的怪书
...this comparative exponential religiosity crap.
你脑子中邪了
It's getting in your brain.
好了，到底发生什么事了，伙计
I mean, what's going on, man?
你相信人会有第二次机会吗？
Do you believe people get second chances?
我，我不知道
L... I don't know.
如果有人犯了错，一个很严重的错误
If somebody makes a mistake, a big mistake...
你认为那个人这辈子…
...do you think that person should have to pay for it...
就该每天为此赎罪吗？
...every day for the rest of their lives?
你是在说你爸的意外吗？
Are you talking about your daddy's accident?
这个嘛
Well...
我只是在寻找一种征兆
I'm just looking for a sign.
什么样的征兆？
What kind of sign?
证明我可以挽回过去
That I can take a negative and turn it into a positive.
我也可以有第二次机会
That I can have a second chance too.
JB，之前你父亲发生意外不是你的错
JB, what happened way back when to your daddy was not your fault.
你知道的，对吗？
You know that, right?
听着，至少答应我你会考虑把车撤掉
Look, at least promise me you'll think about taking the cars out.
我会考虑的
I'll think about it.
我知道你在这里，我可以嗅到你的恐惧
I knew you were here. I could smell your fear.
你好，格雷希尔(地魔)！
Hello, Gressil.
你来这干嘛？
Why are you here?
瓦洛(水魔)！
Wallow.
你为何召唤我们？
And what do you want from us?
我是来找圣凡冈萨的契约的
I've come for the contract of San Venganza.
传说中，那份契约被偷后
Legend has it that the contract was stolen and hidden...
被藏在附近的墓地里
...in a graveyard not far from here.
你们可以帮我找到它
And now you're gonna help me find it.
阿比戈尔（风魔）
Abigor.
找到之后要怎样？
And when we find it, then what?
之后我们就能主宰这世界
Then we'll take this world...
一个城市
...one city...
一个城市的慢慢来
...at a time.
黑心魔！
Blackheart!
- 你在这干什么？ - 我的时代来临了，老家伙
- What the hell are you doing here? - It's my time now, old man.
你的时代会来临的，却不是现在
Your time will come. But not now.
你我都清楚，在这你伤害不了我
We both know you can't harm me here.
我不像你，我决不会失败 以后也不会失败
I'm not like you. I've never fallen. I never will.
在这个世界，我的力量不如你 不过我的骑士却力量雄厚
I may not have power over you in this world, but my rider does.
灵魂骑士？
The Ghost Rider?
你最喜爱的作品？
Your favorite creation?
把地狱之火的力量 浪费在一个可怜的人类身上？
The power of hellfire wasted on a pathetic human?
如果你信任我…
If you had trusted me...
如果你给予我应得的的力量…
...if you had given me what was rightfully mine...
在世界末日到来之前，一切都属于我
It's all mine. Until the end of days.
来吧
Go ahead.
派你的骑士来吧
Send the rider.
我会亲手把他埋了
I'll bury him.
然后再把你埋了
And then I'll bury you.
父亲
Father.
女士们，先生们 欢迎来到爆火强尼的飞越死神秀
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to the Johnny Blaze Leap of Death!
（飞越球场）
耶！
Yeah!
爆火强尼！
Johnny B!
喂！JB！
Hey, JB.
嘘！你打断凯伦的歌声了
You're stepping on Karen.
你刚刚想说什么，麦克？
What was it you were gonna say, Mack?
我重新检查了一下起跳板，看起来还可以
I just ran a second check on the ramps. They look good.
观众有点失控
Crowd's kind of out of control.
强尼，你知道你并不需要这么做吧？
Johnny, you know you don't have to do this, don't you?
这衣服合身吗？感觉有点大！
Does this suit fit all right? Feels a little loose.
很合身
Suit's fine.
帮我拿一下头盔好吗，麦克？ 谢谢
Would you bring me my hat, Mack? Thank you.
你不能活在恐惧中
You can't live in fear.
好，一直靠右走！
All right, we're up here on the right.
爆火先生 我是活动新闻部的安妮.珮吉
Mr. Blaze. Amy Page, event publicity.
- 有时间做个简短的访问吗 - 我不知道你…
- Have time for a quick interview? - I don't know how long...
你进这行有多久了 爆火强尼是从来不接受访问的
...you been doing your job, but Johnny Blaze don't do interviews.
就连老朋友也不行吗？
Not even for an old friend?
你好，强尼！
Hey, Johnny.
嗨！
Hi.
我接受采访
I'll do it.
补妆
Makeup.
他不用
He's good.
噢，你在打量这身行头
Oh, you're looking at the suit.
我知道它看上去很蠢，但粉丝们喜欢 所以我得穿着它
I know it's silly, but the fans like it, so I keep on wearing it.
- 那拐杖怎么解释 - 靠它来支撑身体
- What about the cane? - I need support.
不，这是服装的一部分
No. It's part of the costume.
好，准备，五，四，三，二…
Okay, and ready in five, four, three, two...
你爸还好吗？
How's your dad?
爆火强尼！谢谢你愿意在 这么重要的演出之前接受我们的采访
Johnny Blaze, thank you for talking to us before your big jump.
从来没有人尝试过这么远距离的飞越
No one has ever attempted such a distance before:
飞越三百英尺长的足球场
Three hundred feet from field goal to field goal.
你现在的心里在想什么？
What's going through your mind right now?
你美呆了，我在电视上看到你了
You look really good. I've seen you on TV.
你知道，我常看电视，你的表现很棒
You know, I watch a lot of TV and you do a really good job.
强尼 是什么让你愿意冒险娱乐大众呢？
Johnny, what drives somebody to risk their life for entertainment?
听说你结婚了
I heard you got married.
没有，我没结
Oh, no. No, it didn't happen.
没有…噢…
No?
大多媒体都会关注你所付出的代价
Most of the time the press focuses on the crashes, the broken bones...
例如撞车，骨折！
...the costs of what you do.
除此以外还有其他代价吗？
Are there any other costs?
有的！
Yeah.
好吧！那…
Okay, well...
谢谢你让我们分享爆火强尼的内心世界
Thank you for this revealing peek into the life of Johnny Blaze.
罗姗·辛普森，现场报道！
I'm Roxanne Simpson, on scene.
好，完成！
And we're out.
- 你会留下来看表演吗？ - 哦，我们得赶回去了
- You're gonna stay for the jump, right? - You know, we gotta get back.
更何况，我从来不喜欢看你表演
Plus, I never liked watching you jump.
- 求你了 - 该走了
- Please. - Let's go, guys.
罗姗？
Roxanne?
- 拜托，就签一下 - 你得回到你的座位上去
- Come on, just one signature. - You need to get back to your seat.
- 别推啊 - 好吧
- You don't have to push. - All right.
我敢说你们两个过去肯定有段情史
I'm gonna go out on a limb and say you two had some kind of history.
就是她，麦克！
That was it, Mack.
那个征兆！
The sign.
征兆？
The sign?
- 你确定不留下来一会儿？ - 不！
- Sure you don't wanna stick around? - No.
表演还没开始
It hasn't started yet.
要不我请你吃甜甜圈吧！
I'll buy you a doughnut.
拜托，罗珊 那可是爆火强尼啊！
Come on, Roxie, it's Johnny Blaze.
走吧！
Let's go.
谢天谢地，你总算听我劝 把车子撤掉了
Thank God you listened to me, took the cars out.
不然这简直就是自杀行为
It would've been suicide otherwise.
现在这样，万一你跳不过去
This way if you come up short, see...
你可以掉到一片，松软的，绿…
...you'll come down on some nice, soft, green...
草上
...grass.
爆火强尼将不会如预期的那样 跳越50辆车子
Johnny Blaze will not be jumping 50 cars today as scheduled...
取而代之的是跳跃 6台UH-60黑鹰直升机
...but instead will be leaping six UH-60 Black Hawk helicopters.
从来没人尝试过如此大胆的表演
Never before has any man attempted such a death-defying stunt.
我把车撤了
I took the cars out.
为什么？为什么，JB？ 为什么不先跟我商量？
Why? Why, JB? Why wouldn't you tell me?
- 因为你肯定会生气的 - 你可以叫我老古董
- Because you would have thrown a fit. - Call me old-fashioned...
我这方面是挺可笑 但这种拿人当祭品的行为让我很不舒服
...l'm funny that way. Human sacrifice makes me uncomfortable.
为什么，JB？ 为什么一定要是直升机？
Why, JB? Why helicopters, man?
你知道我在想什么吗？ 一个新的特技
You know what I've been thinking about? A new stunt.
但不是用车子或火圈
But instead of the cars or the ring of fire...
而是用直升机
...a helicopter.
我爸认为这样会很酷
My dad thought it'd be cool.
- 他说对了 - 是啊！
- He was right. - Yeah.
好，好，那我们这样安排吧
Okay. Okay. This is the deal, man.
我要你到起跳板中段时 按下氮气加速系统，知道吗？
Halfway down the ramp I want you to hit the NOS, okay?
别太早按了
Do not hit the NOS too early.
如果你太早加速 你就完蛋了，知道吗？
If you hit it too early, you are screwed. You got that?
JB，你到底有没有在听啊？
Hey, JB, where's your head at, man?
她大概在高速公路上了吧？
She's probably on the interstate by now, huh?
你加了多少氮气？
How much NOS did you put in the tanks?
足够让航天飞机蒙羞了 说吧，凯斯！
Enough to shame the space shuttle. Chief, go ahead.
噢，天啊，他做不到的
Oh, God. He ain't gonna make it.
他做到了
He made it!
我就说他做的到嘛 好啊，JB！
I told you he'd make it! Yeah, JB!
为之鼓掌吧，女士们，先生们
Let's hear it for him, ladies and gentlemen.
三百英尺，是一个只有爆火强尼 才能达到的世界纪录
Three hundred feet! A world record, as only Johnny Blaze can do!
耶！耶！
Yeah! Yeah!
他要去哪里？
Where's he going?
关于那家伙，其他的不说 可他的胆子可真大！
I'll say one thing about the guy, he's got guts.
我说，之前我有一天正好在看个体育节目
I mean, the other day I was watching this, like, sports show...
斯图尔特 可不可以不要再讨论爆火强尼了
Stuart, can you please stop talking about Johnny Blaze already?
这… 恐怕有点困难
Yeah, that might be a little hard.
我做到了
I made it!
- 停一下车吧 - 要我停车吗？
- Pull over! - Do you want me to pull over?
- 继续开 - 好，继续开…
- Drive. - Driving.
拜托，罗珊，我有话跟你说
Come on, Roxie, I need to talk to you.
你叫什么名字？
What's your name?
- 什么？ - 你叫什么名字？
- What? - What's your name?
哦，斯图尔特！
Oh, Stuart!
- 强尼 - 啊，你好！
- Johnny. - Hi.
斯图尔特，你可以帮个忙吗？
Well, Stuart, can you help me out here?
对不起，伙计… 这里她做主
Sorry, dude. She's the boss.
强尼，小心！
Johnny, look out!
好吧，我知道我该怎么办了 等着…
All right, I guess I see how it's gonna be. Hang on!
你好！你好！你好！你好！
Howdy. Howdy, howdy, howdy.
你想自杀吗？
Are you trying to kill yourself?
我想跟你谈谈 我们已经有五万六千年没见了
I wanna talk to you. I haven't seen you in 56,000 years.
这太疯狂了，你是个疯子
This is crazy. You are crazy.
知道吗，强尼？我没时间管这事 我还有稿子要编
I don't have time for this, I have a story to edit.
你可以拒绝的
You could have said no.
他们提出要你采访我的时候 你大可以拒绝的
When they asked you to interview me, you could have said no.
- 把你的车子移开 - 你想说什么？
- Move your van out of the way! - What are you trying to say?
我不是想说什么 我是说，这一定有它的含义
Well, I'm not trying to say anything. I'm saying that means something.
- 抱歉！ - 别管他们，没事
- Sorry! - Don't mind them, they're fine.
我们现在可是停在高速公路上
We are on the side of the freeway.
一起吃晚饭吧 你还是喜欢吃…意大利菜？
Let's get some dinner. You still like Italian?
你到底想怎么样，强尼？ 想做个了结吗？
What's this about, Johnny? You want some closure?
听着，你那时候才十七岁 你遭遇了一场悲剧，所以逃走了
Look, you were 17 and you witnessed a tragedy and you ran.
我明白，我当时就明白了
I understand now like I understood then...
我没对你抱任何恨意，一点也没有
...and I have no hard feelings, none.
什么叫过去，就是已经过去了 完成了，结束了
That's why they call it the past, because it's passed. It's done, it's over with.
太过火了？
Too much?
我住的酒店里有家餐厅 广场餐厅，八点整
There's a restaurant in my hotel, the Plaza. Eight o'clock.
好耶！
Yes!
不准迟到
Don't be late.
这是个征兆，罗姗
This is a sign, Roxanne.
不会有意外的
There are no accidents.
这是命运
Destiny and all that.
强尼，强尼！
Johnny! Johnny! Johnny!
- 可以帮我妹妹签个名吗？ - 当然
- Can you please sign my sister's book? - Oh, sure.
- 三百英尺 - 我们爱你
- 300 feet. - We love you.
嗯，谢谢
Well, thank you.
是三百英尺，太酷了
Three hundred feet. Pretty neat, pretty neat.
好极了，强尼
Right on, Johnny.
谢谢
Thank you.
（0条信息）
你不能活在恐惧中
You can't live in fear.
你成功了，别人都做不到
You made that jump. No one else made that jump.
你是最优秀的车手
You're the best rider.
你应该得到第二次机会的
You deserve a second chance.
她绝对是个预兆
She's a sign.
强尼
Johnny.
好吧！
Okay.
强尼
Johnny.
你
You.
你好啊，强尼！
Hello, Johnny.
离我远一点
Stay away from me.
现在说这些是不是太迟了
Little late for that.
很漂亮的车子
Nice bike.
你来做什么？
Why are you here?
我一直都在这里啊，强尼
Oh, I've always been here, Johnny.
一直都在
All along.
凤凰城
Phoenix...
丹佛
...Denver...
休士顿
...Houston.
果然是你，每次都不让我死
It was you. Keeping me alive.
不，不，强尼
No. No, Johnny.
那全都靠你自己
It's all you.
你是最棒的
You're the best.
而我，是你最狂热的车迷
And I'm your greatest fan.
海报，电玩游戏
The posters, the video games...
人们都在激动的喊叫着
...the crowds screaming, chanting:
强尼
"Johnny.
Johnny.
强尼
Johnny."
这让我多么骄傲啊
It makes me so proud.
就像是看着自己的投资
It's like watching an investment...
一天一天的升值
...that keeps growing and growing...
直到要兑现的那一天
...until the day you cash it in.
那就是今天了，强尼！
That day is today, Johnny.
去找一个叫黑心魔的人
Find the one known as Blackheart...
然后杀了他
...and destroy him.
自己去找
Find him yourself.
这样可不行
Doesrt work like that.
你跟我签了约的，忘了吗?
You're under contract, remember?
如果你成功了
If you succeed...
我就把灵魂还给你
...l'll return your soul.
我不会做的
Yeah, I'm not doing it.
你别无选择
You don't have any choice.
喂！
Hey.
你们不能进来这里 这地方属于私人…
You can't come in here. This is private...
产业
...property.
这里曾经是块墓地？
There was a cemetery here.
哦，是的！很久以前了
Yeah, a long time ago.
那些坟墓怎么了？
What happened to the graves?
被移走了
They moved them.
移去哪去了？
Where?
- 我不知道 - 谁会知道？
- I don't know. - Who would?
嗯…圣米迦勒教堂
Saint Michael's church.
他们负责处理这件事的
They're in charge of the whole thing.
听着，你们真的不该进来
Look, you really shouldn't be here.
这话我听多了
That's what they keep telling me.
上帝啊！
God!
在找人吗？
Looking for someone?
滚回地狱去！
Back to hell.
看来我们没有必要再谈什么了，是吗？
We're not gonna have a meaningful conversation now, are we?
你给我下去
You're going down.
我可不这么想
I don't think so.
（我车开的如何）
他也不怎么样嘛
He ain't so tough.
喂！臭家伙
Hey. Dirtbag.
发发慈悲吧
Have mercy.
抱歉，对你没有
Sorry. All out of mercy.
救我！
Help me!
等一下
Wait.
你觉得我漂亮吗？
You think I'm pretty, right?
他妈的！
Oh, God.
把包给我
Give me the damn bag!
救命！
Help!
谢谢
Thanks.
你！
You.
有罪！
Guilty.
看着我的眼睛
Look into my eyes.
你的灵魂被无辜者的鲜血所污染
Your soul is stained by the blood of the innocent.
感受一下他们的痛苦吧
Feel their pain.
不！
No!
把钱包给我
Give me your wallet!
我们走
Let me go!
（挚爱的父亲爆火巴顿）
早啊，骷髅头
Morning, bonehead.
（卡特史雷，愿天使引领）
- 你好点了吗？ - 是的，好多了
- You all right? - Yeah, I'm good.
我觉得好像全身着了火 谢谢你的水
I feel like my skull's on fire, but I'm good. Thanks for the water.
你看到我的摩托车了吗？
Did you see my bike?
我说的话好笑吗？
Did I say something funny?
是讽刺
Ironic.
我们这里都爱讽刺人
We're big on irony around here.
- 摩托车在那间屋子里 - 谢谢
- It's out by the shed. - Thanks.
它很正常
It does.
什么？
What?
你怀疑你的摩托车是不是正常？ 很正常
You're wondering if your bike looks normal? It does.
还有，回答你另一个问题
And to answer your other questions:
昨晚的事是真的
Last night did happen...
那不是梦
...it wasrt a dream...
而且它会再次发生的
...and it will happen again.
你到底是谁？
Who are you?
问题是…，你又是谁？
Question is, who are you?
你就是传说中的骑士，灵魂骑士
You are the Rider. The Ghost Rider.
快点习惯吧，那样会好过一点
Get used to it, kid. It'll be a lot easier.
不然，我有块墓地刚好适合你
If you don't, I got a nice cozy spot picked out for you.
他们已经看到你了 他们会等着你的
They've seen you now. They'll be waiting for you.
你想活命就需要我帮忙
You'll need my help, you expect to last the night.
上次我让一个陌生人帮我，结果却不怎么好
Last time I let a stranger help me it didn't pan out so good.
这不是你想逃就逃得了的事
This ain't something you can run from, kid.
签下契约就已经注定了会有今天
This day has been coming since you made that deal.
恭喜你！
Congratulations.
你成功的机会刚从零改为渺茫
Your chances just went from none to slim.
根据可靠消息
Sources close to the investigation say that there may be a link...
这次在市中心所发生的事件很可能
...between what happened here in downtown...
跟之前在沙漠里发生的大屠杀事件有关联
...and the Broken Spoke massacre in the desert.
罗姗·辛普森，现场报导！
I'm Roxanne Simpson on scene.
好，完成！
And we're out.
- 多兰警官 - 无可奉告
- Captain Dolan. - No comment.
之前发生的大屠杀
Is it true they found a connection between the massacre...
跟昨晚的事件真的有关吗？
...and last night's victim here at the city train yards?
无可奉告
No comment.
私下谈谈
Off the record, captain.
私下谈谈？
Off the record?
滚蛋
Piss off.
灵魂骑士是恶魔的赏金猎人
The Rider is the devil's bounty hunter.
专门负责收集那些从地狱逃脱的灵魂
Sent to hunt down anyone that escapes from hell.
帮我消毒
Sterilize that for me.
消毒
Sterilize.
用开水
In the boiling water.
好吧
Right. Okay.
我有点困惑
Little confused.
在白天你会是正常人
During the day you'll be normal.
但一到夜晚
But at night...
当你面对邪恶时
...in the presence of evil...
你就会变成骑士
...the Rider takes over.
我想起来了
I remember now.
昨晚
Last night.
那是个小混混…
There was some punk...
我可以看到他所犯的一切罪恶
...and I could see all the wrong he'd ever done...
并且把这些罪加注在他身上
...and I turned it all against him.
忏悔之眼
The Penance Stare.
那能灼烧罪恶之魂
It sears the souls of the wicked.
这是灵魂骑士最厉害的武器
It's the Ghost Rider's greatest weapon.
所有的骑士都有这种能力
All the Riders have it.
还有其他人 跟我遇到了相同的麻烦？
Have there been others with my "Ghost Rider" problem?
有几个
Been a few.
上一个已经是150年前的事了
Last one was 150 years ago...
在一个名为圣凡冈萨的小镇上
...in a little town called San Venganza.
很好的小镇
Nice town.
很友好的人
Nice people.
直到有个陌生人跑来
Till a stranger came along making promises...
和村民订下契约
...one deal at a time.
被贪婪所驱使的人们开始互相残杀
Consumed by greed, they turned on one another...
直到圣凡冈萨被淹没在自己的鲜血中
...until the village of San Venganza drowned in its own blood...
而那些灵魂 被永久的困在那个被上帝遗忘的地方
...their souls trapped forever in that godforsaken place.
这跟黑心魔有什么关系？
What's this have to do with Blackheart?
黑心魔？
Blackheart?
他要你对付黑心魔？
He sent you after Blackheart?
还有其他几个
And others.
放逐之魔
The Hidden.
他们都是被圣米迦勒逐出天堂的堕落天使
Fallen angels cast out of heaven by Saint Michael himself.
他们藏身自然元素之中，等待着世界末日的到来
They hide within the elements waiting for the end of days.
你最好待在这里，孩子
You better hang around here, kid.
他们无法进入这块圣地
They can't come onto hallowed ground.
谢谢
Thanks.
还有，谢谢你提供的消息
And thanks for the info.
知道我是恶魔的赏金猎人 感觉好多了
I feel much better now that I know I'm the devil's bounty hunter.
- 你要去哪里？ - 有个人我一定得见一面
- Where you going? - Somebody I gotta see.
这是个坏决定
That's a bad idea.
反正也不是第一次了
Wouldrt be my first.
你为什么那么做？
Why'd you do it?
为什么签下那份契约？
Why'd you make the deal?
我当时只是个孩子
I was a kid.
那你得到了什么？
What'd you get in return?
痛苦
Heartache.
队长，队长
Captain. Captain!
骑车人和加油站经理身上的痕迹
Forensics on the bikers and the station manager...
表明死因相同
...suggest the same cause of death.
硫磺中毒？
Sulfur poison?
- 我想硫磺是没有毒的 - 大剂量时就有毒
- I didn't think sulfur was toxic. - It is, in massive doses.
这些人被淹没在硫磺里
And these guys were swimming in it.
可能是有人用化学武器袭击
Could be the work of a chemical attack.
或者是宗教狂热分子所为
Or a religious nut.
嘿，我认识你，我在…
Hey. I know you. I've seen...
这里没什么能表明是宗教性质的
Okay? There's nothing here to suggest any kind of religious m.o.
- 硫磺？ - 怎么了？
- Sulfur? - What about it?
读过《旧约》吗？
Ever read the Old Testament?
硫磺烈火 （用以惩罚有罪者的地狱之火）
Brimstone.
没错
There you go.
哦，天啊
Oh, my God.
很难形容今早这里遭到的破坏
It's hard to describe the destruction here this morning.
麻烦你们往后站
Can I get you people to stand back, please?
我不清楚，看上去像是超自然力量
I don't know. It seems like something supernatural.
你可以跟我们描述一下救你的人吗？
Could you tell us about the Good Samaritan?
嗯，首先我是绝对不会忘记他的
Well, I'll never forget him, that's for sure.
他个子高高的，肩膀很宽 皮包骨的那种瘦
He was tall, broad shoulders, and thin, really thin, like bony.
他骑着一辆很炫的车，全是火焰
And he had this rad chopper, it was all flames and stuff.
还有，他的脸是个骷髅，还冒着火
Oh, and his face was a skull and it was on fire.
冒火？
"On fire."
是的，像是…
Yeah, like:
哗哗…那么大的火
Like that much fire.
而且，可能这听起来有点怪 不过那挺适合他的
And I know it sounds weird, but it looked okay on him.
我是说，他的打扮很前卫，可是他超帅的
I mean, it was an edge look but he totally pulled it off.
听来很不可思议
Not sure what to add to that.
罗姗·辛普森，现场报导！
I'm Roxanne Simpson on scene.
谢谢
Thanks.
- 罗珊… - 别
- Roxie... - Don't.
不，等一下，让我道歉
Now, hold on a second. Let me apologize.
- 昨晚的事，我实在不敢求你原谅 - 你不需要道歉
- Last night was inexcusable. - No apologies.
知道吗？你昨晚帮了我一个大忙
See, you did me a favor last night...
因为，你让我想起过去，现在
...because you made me think of then and now.
你走的那一天，是的 我哭得像快死了一样
And when you left, yeah, it hurt like hell.
但是你知道吗？我熬过了
But you know what? I got over it...
然后我上了大学 找到了一份好工作
...and I went to college, I got a great job.
但你呢，强尼？
But you, Johnny...
还是老样子
...you're just the same.
也许你现在收入高了，粉丝也多了
Oh, better paid, more fans...
但你还是个耍杂技的
...but you're still just a carny.
没错
Yeah.
噢
Oh, man.
看来我爸说对了
My dad was right.
你只是一段插曲罢了
You were just a phase.
口才不错
That went well.
队长，我有新发现
Hey, captain! I got something.
（浮世烩）
世界末日
"End of days.
寄主可以通过
The host can gain control of the possessing spirit...
对人体自身固有的火元素的专注与操控
...through concentration on and manipulation of...
逐步控制其所占据的灵魂
...the fire element that exists within man."
我现在命令我内心的火焰
I am speaking to the fire element within me.
给我控制自己灵魂的力量
Give me control over the possessing spirit.
- 嗨！ - 嗨！
- Hi. - Hi.
希望你不介意，但你的电梯没上锁
Hey, I hope you don't mind. Your lift was open.
我是来道歉的
I came to apologize.
我今晚就要离开这个城市了
I'm leaving town tonight...
我不希望今天所说的话 是我们的告别词
...and I didn't want what I said today to be the last words between us.
- 没关系 - 不，有关系
- That's okay. - No, it's not.
那些话太残忍，而且完全不真实
It was cruel and totally untrue.
所以我觉得很过意不去
And I feel really terrible about it.
不，真的没关系
Please, don't. It's okay.
有东西烧焦了吗？
Is something burning?
可能是我邻居的烧烤炉
Oh, that must be coming from outside. Neighbor's hibachi.
比尔，他刚买了一个
Bill, he just got it.
我还保留着那个
I still have that one.
什么？
You what?
那个我也有
I have that one, too.
我记得那天
I remember that day.
有很多人排队…
There were a dozen people waiting in line...
而你却投了成堆的铜板
...and you went through a whole roll of quarters.
看我的表情，看得出我在害怕
Look at my face. You can tell I was just terrified...
怕我爸随时会进来
...that my dad was gonna come in any second.
好了，我想
Okay, I just...
我…我还是送你回车上吧！
It's just... I think I should walk you to your car.
现在不是时候
See, it's not great timing.
首先，你为了约我出去 差点撞死在高速公路上
You almost kill yourself on the highway...
但你却没来赴约
...so you can ask me out and then you don't show.
然后你一直保留着我的照片…
Then you keep my picture...
但是当我吻你的时候，你又想推我出去
...but when I kiss you, you try to shove me out the door. What's...
这到底是怎么回事？
What's going on?
你难道一点也不在乎我吗，强尼？
Don't you care about me at all, Johnny?
你知道你可以告诉我的 什么都可以跟我说
You know you can talk to me. You can tell me anything.
拜托
Please.
反正你也不会相信我的
You wouldn't believe me anyway.
试试看
Try me.
你会以为我是个疯子
You'll think I'm crazy.
也许我真的疯了
Maybe I am crazy.
我希望我疯了
I hope I'm crazy.
我做这行见多识广 我什么奇怪的事情都遇见过
In my job, I've seen and heard just about everything.
你说什么也吓不倒我的
So there is nothing you can tell me that's gonna surprise me.
不会录下来吧？
Off the record?
不会
Yeah.
我把我的灵魂卖给了魔鬼
I sold my soul to the devil.
现在我得保护你
And now I have to spare you.
谁会伤害我？
Spare me from what?
恶魔，因为我为他工作
The devil, on account of I work for him.
所以我没办法赴晚餐的约会
That's why I couldn't make it to dinner.
因为你在为恶魔工作？
Because you were working for the devil?
是的！我是他的赏金猎人
Well, yeah. I'm his bounty hunter.
但这只会在晚上发生，像现在那样
But it only happens at night, like it is right now.
只要当我面对邪恶时
Whenever I'm around evil.
恶人，恶灵什么的 我就会变成…
Evil people, evil spirits. I change into...
什么？
What?
一只，一只怪物 不过我正在学习
Just a great big monster, but I am learning to...
正在努力学习怎么控制它
I'm getting control of it.
正在尝试
I'm trying to.
所以今晚，你也会…
So tonight, you'll...
我想是的
I believe so.
所以你应该…
Which is why it's probably a very good idea...
应该赶紧回去，罗珊
...that you run on home now, Roxie.
你是认真的？
You're serious.
这就是你的解释？
So this is your excuse?
为过去？为昨晚？为所有的事情？
For the past? For last night? For everything?
我想我现在有两种选择
The way I see it is I've got a couple of choices:
第一，我可以相信你，真的认为你跟我说的都是真的
I could either accept that you really believe what you're telling me is true...
然后把你带到最近的精神病院去
...and take you to the nearest psychiatric hospital.
你看吧…
You see, now that...
第二，我发现你宁可编个如此离谱的烂故事
Or I realize that you'd rather make up ridiculous stories...
也不愿意跟我说真话
...than be honest with me...
我会走出这道门
...and I walk out of that door...
再也不回来
...forever.
- 不许动！ - 把手举起来！
- Don't move! - Hands up!
手举过头顶
Hands where we can see them! Right over your head.
爆火强尼
Johnny Blaze.
是的
Yeah.
我是杰克·多兰警官 这位是爱德华刑警
Captain Jack Dolan. This is Officer Edwards.
你得跟我们走
You're coming with us.
好吧
Okay.
让我们再来一遍
Let's try this again.
我们在犯罪现场发现了你的车轮印
We have your plate and the tread from your tires at the crime scene.
我们有个证人可以作证…
We have a witness who will testify...
嫌疑犯使用某种火的效果
...that the suspect used some kind of fire effect.
这种效果跟你的特技表演所用的是一样的
An effect just like the ones that you use in your stunt shows!
没错，但我告诉你了，我没杀过任何人
Yeah. But I told you, I didn't kill anybody.
- 这个人呢？你记得他吗？ - 不记得
- What about him, you remember him? - No.
这个人三年以后就退休了
This guy was three years from retirement...
生前连一只苍蝇也没有伤害过
...never harmed a fly.
事实上，这些人都是在你…
In fact, neither did most of the corpses turning up...
回家之后死的，你这个狗娘养的
...since you came home, you son of a bitch.
- 我没有杀人 - 胡说！
- I didn't kill anybody. - Bullshit!
好吧！我们放松一下
Okay, let's take a breather.
- 这可真热 - 热？
- It's warm in here. - Warm?
我都快着火了，你不是吗？
Yeah, I'm burning up. Arert you?
有点
A little.
要抽烟吗？
You want a cigarette?
好吧
Okay.
介意我抽吗？
Mind if I do?
刚才太奇怪了
Okay, that was weird.
听着，强尼，我不是要你帮我们
Look, Johnny, I'm not asking for your help.
我是要你帮你自己
I'm asking you to help yourself.
我常看电视 我知道你们在做什么
I watch a lot of TV and I know what you're doing.
一个扮白脸，一个扮黑脸 但你们两个都是好警察
Good cop, bad cop. But you're both good cops.
你们的服务对社会很重要
And you provide a very, very important civil service.
其实，我也想过在我的特技生涯结束后
In fact, when I finish my stunt career...
我会利用我的技术成为一名摩托车巡警
...I intend to apply my skills to being a motorcycle policeman.
所以我很想帮你们 但我真的没杀人
So I'd love to help you. But I didn't kill anybody.
噢，上帝！
Jesus Christ.
你想说服谁，强尼？ 我们还是你自己？
Who you trying to convince, Johnny? Us or yourself?
我们在这尽力帮你
We're trying to help you here.
我们尽力让这件事了无声息
We're trying to keep this thing quiet.
没错，因为我认为你的粉丝
Yeah, because I imagine that your fans wouldn't be too keen...
不会希望你牵涉到谋杀案的调查
...on you being wrapped up in a homicide investigation.
更别提那些赞助商，活动主办者…
Not to mention all those corporate sponsors, event promoters...
你现在愿意说了吗？强尼
You ready to talk now, Johnny?
否则你就得在这过夜了
Or do you want to spend the night in the tank?
哦，我可不想那样
Oh, I don't wanna do that.
我当然不想
No, sir. I sure don't wanna do that.
但是我没有杀任何人
But I didn't kill anybody.
可恶！
Damn it!
你一定要放我走，真正的凶手正逍遥法外
You gotta let me go. The real killer's out there.
- 这是谁啊 - 听着，你们搞错了
- Lookie here. - But you're making a mistake.
看看谁来了？
What've we got?
快走！
Come on, move your ass!
爆火强尼来看我们了
Blaze, riding up to meet us.
哦，天啊，求求你 你不会真想把我关在这吧
Oh, God. Oh, please. Please, you don't wanna put me in there.
抱歉，五星级酒店都客满了
Sorry, the Ritz was booked.
天…拜托，快放我出去
Oh, God. Please, get me out of here!
你长得很像那个爆火强尼
You look like that Johnny Blaze.
是的，常有人这么说
Yeah, yeah, I hear that a lot.
不，你就是他
Nah, that is you.
- 就是他！ - 没错
- That's him! - Yeah, it is.
我几年前去看过你的表演
I saw you jump in the state fair a few years ago.
那时候我花了十块钱想看你脑浆四溅
I paid 10 bucks to watch you splatter.
结果你没有
But you didn't.
看来有人有麻烦了
Looks like somebody's tripping out.
也许你在外面是个名人，强尼
You might be a big shot out there, Blaze...
但在这里你只是一只被关在笼子里的猴子！
...but in here you're nothing but a monkey in a cage!
我不想惹麻烦
Now, I don't want any trouble.
I don't want any trouble.
看来是麻烦找上了你
Looks like trouble just found you.
不错的外套
Nice jacket.
拜托，放过他吧
Come on, man, leave him alone.
滚开！
Get lost!
- 这外套是我的了 - 住手！
- The jacket's mine. - Stop it!
不错的外套
Nice jacket.
很不错
Very nice.
你
You.
无罪！
Innocent.
请原谅我，神父，我有罪
Forgive me, Father, for I have sinned.
罪孽深重
I've sinned a lot.
不许动！
Hold it!
（车库）
（怒火）
圣凡冈萨的契约到底在哪里？
Where's the contract of San Venganza?
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you are talking about.
别想骗我，多年来你守护着它，保守秘密
Don't lie to me! You've been protecting it all these years, sworn to secrecy.
我发誓会保密的，尤其是对你这种人
Sworn to keep it from the likes of you!
古谚有云
There's an old saying:
“千万不要养虎贻患”
"Raise no more devils than you can lay down."
我老爸养我就中计了
My father raised one too many.
呼叫各小队，重刑犯逃往闹市区
Calling all units. Reported 10-50 in the downtown area.
请小心警戒
Proceed with caution.
他来抓我们了
He's coming for us.
阿比戈尔
Abigor.
你知道该怎么做
You know what to do.
骑士
Rider.
我发现嫌疑犯在樱桃街上向西驶去 重复，樱桃街，向西驶去
I have a suspect fleeing west on Cherry. Repeat, west on Cherry.
- 那是条死巷子，你抓到他了 - 知道
- That's a dead end. You got him. - 10-4 on that.
嫌疑犯现在的位置在哪里？
What's the suspect's location?
- 上面 - 什么？
- Up. - What?
嫌疑犯在往上走
The suspect is going up.
哦，天啊
Oh, my God.
救救我
People, help me.
快，快，快
Go, go, go!
包围他！围成一圈！上！
Surround him! Make a perimeter! Let's go!
请让开
Come in, please.
- 过来！ - 不！
- Come here! - No!
你惹火我了
You're pissing me off.
好，好
Okay, okay.
对不起
Sorry.
靠右站
Take a right.
你应该加入我们的，骑士
You should've joined us, Rider.
我们很快就能够找到那份契约了
Soon we will have the contract...
然后，你会成为新地狱历史的脚注
...and then you'll only be a footnote in the history of the new hell.
该是清理空气的时候了
Time to clear the air.
你是真笨还是假笨？骑士
You're a slow learner, aren't you, Rider?
你是无法抓住风的！
You cannot catch the wind!
不！
No!
哦，天啊
Oh, my God.
强尼
Johnny.
准备开火！
Prepare to fire!
- 开火！ - 不！
- Fire! - Don't!
他们知道我是谁了
They know who I am.
- 谁知道了？ - 什么？所有的人啊！
- Who's that? - What? Everybody.
你难道不看电视的？ 你这个人是怎么了？
You don't watch TV? What's the matter with you?
这一切会结束吗？
Is this thing ever gonna end?
你抓到他的时候就结束了
Lt'll end if you can catch him.
这到底是怎么回事？
What's really going on?
- 有什么好消息吗？ - 需要我效劳吗，警官？
- Anything good on? - How can I help you, captain?
出去
Get out.
我们昨晚审讯你的一个朋友…
We brought a friend of yours in for questioning last night...
现在他却不见了
...and now he seems to have disappeared.
强尼有以任何方法与你联络吗？女士
Has Johnny Blaze tried to contact you in any way, ma'am?
抱歉，我帮不上忙
Sorry. Can't help, guys.
听着，我不想假装了解发生了什么事
Look, I don't pretend to know what the hell that thing is...
但我确实知道强尼与这事有关
...but I do know that Blaze is wrapped up in it.
唯一能救他的方法就是你现在帮我们找到他
And the only way you can save him now is if you help us find him.
给你六个小时 否则我们就对外宣布我们所知的一切
You got six hours. After that we go public with everything we got.
六个小时
Six hours.
卡特史雷？
"Can'ter Slade."
传说中，他是德克萨斯州的巡警 一个很受人尊敬的人
Legend has it he was a Texas Ranger. Man of honor.
但他后来变的贪婪
But he got greedy.
结果被抓了起来，等待绞刑
Found himself locked up, waiting on the gallows.
有一天，有个陌生人来看他
Stranger came to see him.
承诺会给他自由
Offering freedom.
于是，他们做了交易
Slade made a deal.
他变成了灵魂骑士
Ended up a Ghost Rider.
这件事跟他有什么关系？
What's he gotta do with this?
记得我跟你说的…
Remember that contract the stranger made...
圣凡冈萨的契约吗？
...with the people of San Venganza?
传说后来，卡特史雷被派去收集那里的灵魂
The story goes that Slade was sent there to collect all the souls.
但他在那里所发现的灵魂太邪恶
But what he found there was so evil...
于是，他拿着契约书逃跑了
...that he took the contract and rode off.
他偷了契约？
He stole it.
为了不让“墨菲斯托菲里斯（万魔王）”得到它
Keep Mephistopheles from getting his hands on it.
有人说那份契约已经被他带进棺材了
Some people say he was buried with it.
- 是吗？ - 我不知道
- Was he? - I don't know.
但我知道，黑心魔一定会来 他会不惜一切的得到它
What I do know is that Blackheart is coming, and he'll do anything to get it.
所以你一定要远离亲戚和朋友…
That's why it's important for you to stay away from friends and family...
任何他能用来对付你的人
...anybody he can use against you, because he will.
罗姗
Roxanne.
强尼？
Johnny?
天啊！
God!
对不起！对不起！
Sorry! Sorry!
女士，你吓了我一跳
Ma'am, you gave me a start.
- 我在找强尼 - 我也是
- I'm looking for Johnny. - Yeah. You and me both.
- 他有没有跟你联系？ - 没有
- Have you heard from him? - No.
不过我听说他有麻烦
But I heard he got in trouble.
他被捕了吧？怎么回事？
He got arrested, yeah? What for?
是吗？如果这件事传到媒体那里 他的前途就完了
Yeah, well, if this gets out in the press, his career is over.
相信我，他的前途不算什么
Yeah, trust me, his career's the least of it.
你知道吗？你是个好人，长得也很漂亮
You know, you seem like a nice lady, and you're pretty and all...
不过我们原本一切顺风如意
...but we were riding the gravy train on biscuit wheels...
自从你来了之后就衰事不断
...then you showed up, everything went to hell.
所以，可不可以请你从哪来回哪去
So why don't you go back to wherever it is you came from?
我不能回去，至少目前不行
I can't go back. Not now.
那就请你告诉我到底发生了什么事！
Then tell me what the hell's going on!
我说了你也不会信的
You wouldn't believe me if I told you.
听着，你不了解我
Look, you don't know me...
但我爱他
...but I love him.
所以，如果你有任何可以帮上忙的线索 任何东西…
So if there's anything you know that can help, anything...
最近他常看一些奇怪的书
Lately, he's been reading these really weird books...
那些书把他搞的怪怪的
...and they're messing with his mind.
而且他还做笔记，经常熬夜 他，他就在那里做的
He's writing stuff down and staying up late. And he does it over here.
你可以翻翻看他的东西 但我不知道那有些什么意义
You can go through this stuff, and I don't know if it means anything.
这里是圣地
This is hallowed ground.
你以为我和其他人一样？
Did you think I was like the others?
我拥有我父亲的全部力量 但没有他的一项弱点
I have all of my father's strengths and none of his weaknesses.
新的地狱在圣凡冈萨
The new hell is in San Venganza.
我需要那份契约
I need the contract.
我知道它在这
I know it's here.
现在把它交给我
Now give it to me.
交给我
Give it to me.
Give it to me. Give it to me. Give it to me.
你一定会失败的
You're gonna fall.
就像你父亲
Just like your father.
那个骑士，他在哪里？
The Rider, where is he?
走了！
Gone!
那女孩
The girl.
你要是伤害她，他就会像风暴前的闪电 那样出现在你面前
You hurt her, he'll be there like lightning before the storm.
正合我意
I'm counting on it.
罗姗在哪里？
Where's Roxanne?
伙计，你去哪了？大家都在找…
Dude. Where've you been? Everybody's out looking...
- 她在哪里？ - 她找你去了
- Where is she? - She's out looking for you.
上帝！
Jesus.
还没来呢
Not even close.
你拥有他的心
You have his heart.
现在我要弄碎它
Now I'm gonna break it.
罗姗！
Roxanne?
麦克
Mack.
罗珊！
Roxanne.
看着我的眼睛
Look into my eyes.
你的忏悔之眼对我不起作用的
Your Penance Stare doesn't work on me.
因为我没有灵魂可以让你烧
I have no soul to burn.
你的监护人忘了跟你说了？
I guess the Caretaker forgot to mention that, huh?
吃惊吧！
Surprise!
他让你把我抓回去
He sent you to bring me back.
但我不想回去
I'm not going back.
我喜欢这里
I like it here.
他竟然会认为你能比的过我？
He thinks you're better than me?
我真不知道是谁比较可悲 你，还是他
I don't know who's more pathetic, you or him.
听着，希望你那骷髅脑袋可以记住
Now, listen to me. And try to get it through that thick skull of yours.
从现在起，你不再听命于我父亲 而是帮我做事
You don't work for my father anymore. You work for me.
从你监护人那里把契约拿来
Get the contract from the Caretaker.
拿到圣凡冈萨来给我 我也许会饶你女朋友一命
Bring it to me in San Venganza and maybe I'll spare your girl's life.
还有，强尼
And, Johnny...
别让我等太久了
...don't make me wait.
怎么回事？
What happened?
- 是黑心魔 - 他们抓走了她
- Blackheart. - They got her.
那契约在哪里？ 没有它我没办法了结此事
Where's the contract? I can't end this without it.
好吧，那我就把这里都挖一遍
Just gonna have to dig this whole damn place up myself.
不在那里， 孩子！
It's not there, kid.
圣凡冈萨的契约
Contract of San Venganza.
人间地狱
Hell on earth.
你得信任我才行
Now, you're gonna have to trust me.
为什么？
And why is that?
他也许拥有我的灵魂
He may have my soul...
不过他并没有我的心
...but he doesn't have my spirit.
任何有胆量为爱出卖灵魂的人
Any man who's got the guts to sell his soul for love...
都拥有改变世界的力量
...got the power to change the world.
驱策你的不是贪婪
You didn't do it for greed.
而是正当的理由
You did it for the right reason.
也许那能让上帝站在你这边
Maybe that puts God on your side.
对他来说，那让你更形成威胁
To him, that makes you dangerous.
令你无可预测
Makes you unpredictable.
这对你来说是最好不过了
That's the best thing you can be right now.
圣凡冈萨距离这里有500英里
San Venganza's 500 miles from here.
我们得快点出发
We better get moving.
我们？
"We"?
我想我应该还可以骑最后一次
I got one last ride left in me.
卡特史雷
Can'ter Slade.
你跟得上吗？
Can you keep up?
出发吧
Let's ride.
记得要呆在暗处
Stick to the shadows.
这是我最后一次变身
This is the end of the trail for me.
我的能量已耗尽
I got nothing left.
我只能再变身一次 而我等待的就是这一天
I could only change one more time, and I was saving it for this.
上天知道我犯了多少错
God knows I've made my share of mistakes.
我一直想改正我犯的错
Been trying to make things right ever since.
现在我也只能希望 上天愿给我第二次机会
Guess all I can do now is hope he sees fit to give me a second chance.
谢谢你
Thank you.
不
No.
谢谢你，孩子
Thank you, kid.
骑士要来了
The Rider is coming.
要来救你
Coming to save you.
你认为你可以阻止他？ 没有人可以阻止他
You think you can stop him? Nothing can stop him.
他时间不够了
He's running out of time.
我可以确定
I'll make sure of it.
快要黎明了，让他慢下来
It's almost dawn. Slow him down.
- 什么？ - 让他慢..下..来！
- What? - Slow him down.
惊奇吧
Surprise.
停
Stop.
如果你变身，她就死定了
You change, she dies.
快变身，强尼！
Do it, Johnny.
先让她走
Let her go first.
看来你没时间了
Looks like you're out of time.
这是圣凡冈萨的契约
"This is the contract of San Venganza.
灵魂们
All of you...
都来我这里吧！
...come to me!"
强尼！
Johnny!
我的名字是“群魔”
My name is Legion...
因为我们…
...for we are...
为数众多
...many.
走吧，他已经得到他想要的了
Let's go. He got what he wanted.
你先走，我得到暗处去 我得结束这一切
You go. I gotta get him to the shadows. I gotta end this.
为什么？为什么是你？
Why? Why you?
从我订下契约的那天就已经注定了是我
It's been me since the day I made the deal.
只有我能够同时存在于两个世界
I'm the only one who can walk in both worlds.
我是灵魂骑士
I'm Ghost Rider.
快跑！
Run!
来啊，你这混蛋
Come on, you son of a bitch.
你们的世界
All of your world...
你们的灵魂
...all of your souls...
现在都是我的了
...will be mine now.
- 把枪扔过来！ - 没子弹了！
- Throw me the gun! - It's out!
扔过来！
Throw it!
有那么多恶灵在你身体里是什么感觉？
How does it feel to have all that evil inside of you?
他们的力量
All their power.
他们的灵魂
All their souls.
上千个灵魂等着燃烧
A thousand souls to burn.
看着我的眼睛
Look into my eyes.
你的灵魂被无辜者的鲜血所污染
Your souls are stained by the blood of the innocent.
不
No.
感受他们的痛苦吧
Feel their pain.
圣父、圣子和圣灵
Father, the Son and the Holy Spirit.
我宰了你！
Kill you!
住手！
Stop it!
哦，天啊！
Oh, God!
我是怪物
Monster.
我不怕
I'm not afraid.
恭喜你，强尼！
Congratulations, Johnny.
你已经完成了你的约定
You upheld your end of the bargain.
我该拿回属于灵魂骑士的力量了
It's time I take back the power of the Ghost Rider.
你可以回去过你自己的生活
You get your life back.
你得到了你一直想要的真爱
The love you've always wanted.
可以建立自己的家庭
You can start a family of your own.
世上多的是交易可谈
There are more deals to be made.
有很多人愿意拿灵魂换取欲望
More people willing to give their souls for what they desire.
让别人去承受这个诅咒吧 你自由了
Let someone else carry this curse. You're free now.
毕竟
After all...
说话要算话
...a deal's a deal.
不
No.
我要拥有这个诅咒
I'm gonna own this curse...
并且用它来对付你
...and I'm gonna use it against you.
每当无辜者被牺牲时
Whenever innocent blood is spilt...
我会以父亲之名
...it'll be my father's blood...
出现在你面前
...and you'll find me there.
复仇之魂
A spirit of vengeance...
以火焰对抗火焰
...fighting fire with fire.
我会让你付出代价的
I will make you pay for this.
你不能活在恐惧中
You can't live in fear.
不！
No!
你现在去哪里？
So where will you go now?
命运安排我去哪里就去哪里吧
Wherever the road takes me, I guess.
我爸曾说过:“不主导命运，就会被命运牵着走”
My daddy once said, "If you don't make a choice, the choice makes you."
是吗？但为什么你的选择总是让我们分开？
Yeah. But why do your choices always keep us apart?
我真希望这一切都不一样
Sure wish things could have turned out different.
不，这就是你
No. This is what you are.
这是你该做的
This is what you always were meant to be.
你已经得到了第二次机会
You got your second chance.
好好珍惜它
Go out there and make the best of it.
（强尼罗珊永远相爱）
据说西部是建立在传说上
It's said that the West was built on legends...
而传说协助我们解读
...and that legends are a way of understanding...
比我们更伟大的事物
...things greater than ourselves.
影响我们命运的力量
Forces that shape our lives.
难以解释的事件
Events that defy explanation.
升上天堂的灵魂
Individuals whose lives soar to the heavens...
坠入凡间的生命
...or fall to the earth.
传说就是这样诞生的
This is how legends are born.